<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Euros 2020 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Euros 2020 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 16</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-16/</guid>
      <description>Wales v Denmark Denmark were absolutely brilliant in this game. They will now be facing either Netherlands or Czech Republic. Kasper Dolberg was amazing in the absence of Poulsen and scored a great brace in what is his stadium when playing for Ajax. Wales did look threatening in a the first 10-12 minutes but could not finish their chances. Dolberg first scored with a great curler from outside the box. Later he scored again after a shambolic clearance from the substitue Willams who came on after Roberts pulled his groin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 13</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-13/</guid>
      <description>Sweden v Poland A brilliant thriller from Poland on their last match. Sweden played well and their position in the group has given them a favorable match in the Round of 16 but it may be challenging for them. An early goal from Forsberg gave them the lead with a great finish on his left. Lewa had a chance in the first chance to get back in it when his first header hit the post and he hit the post again on the rebound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 12</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-12/</guid>
      <description>Czech Republic v England England top the group after this win. They were pretty threatening from the get go from Grealish and Saka and Sterling scored with a header after a brilliant ball in by Grealish. After that chances came to the Czechs as well. Pickford made a brilliant save from long range. England did have a few more chances and Henderson actually scored but the touch from Bellingham meant he was offside so it was disallowed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 11</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-11/</guid>
      <description>Finland v Belgium Going into this matchday, Finland still had a chance for being 2nd in the group. That chance is mostly gone if the other match does not go their way. Belgium were absolutely brilliant off the blocks but were denied for a while by the brillant Hradecky. But unfortunately, the last(or second last) contribution he did was score an own goal. The corner came in from Belgium, Vermaelen&amp;rsquo;s header came off the bar and hit Hradecky on the way in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 10</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-10/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine v Austria Austria were wasteful in chance, Ukraine were wasteful in possession. Nevertheless, this means that Austria go through as Team no 2 from Group C. This means they&amp;rsquo;ll be facing Italy in the Round of 16. Austria were looking dangerous from corners and one in particular from Alaba was put in by Baumgartner who is now the youngest scorer in this tournament now. Ukraine wasted a couple good chances but overall they were poor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 9</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-9/</guid>
      <description>Spain v Poland Morata and Moreno made Szczesny look good along with his amazing saves too. Morata missed a few chances before he did score which was given a scare when it was ruled out for offside but was overturned by VAR. Spain were then wasteful. This turned up the pressure and Poland equalised in the second half from none other than Lewandowski. Laporte with a school boy error who got easily pushed by Lewa before heading it in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 8</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-8/</guid>
      <description>England v Scotland I guess you could say this was a moral victory for Scotland given their history. They frustrated England well along with England themselves being wasteful in the rainy pitch. The fans booing didn&amp;rsquo;t help(Atleast there was no reason to play the song now heh. For reference: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RJqimlFcJsM). Scotland had a few decent chances from Che Adams but that was it. Foden missed again, Kane missed, Stones hit the post, Everything went wrong for them in this derby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-7/</guid>
      <description>Netherlands v Austria The Dutch are through. This could have been more convincing with maybe 3 or 4 but it does the job. A penalty from Depay gave the lead and he should&amp;rsquo;ve made it 2 with an easy chance given to him. At the end, another goal from Dumfries gave them the confirmation. Austria never really had all too many chances to talk about.
Sweden v Slovakia This was a fairly even game with chances on both sides but the keepers did well until Dubravka conceded the penalty that gave the Swedes the lead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-6/</guid>
      <description>Italy v Switzerland Italy are through with yet another 3-0 win in a dominant showing. Locatelli becoming the first Italian since Balotelli to score a brace in the Euros which capped off a great performance from the youngster. Immobile capped it off with a brilliant goal as well
Ukraine v North Macedonia Ukraine did well in this game dominating and scoring 2 great goals. Second half was fairly even with both sides getting chances but denied by their respective keepers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-4/</guid>
      <description>Hungary v Portugal I HAVE NO PITY TOWARDS HUNGARY. God, this game was hard to watch. Portugal were frustrated heavily by Hungary who were ultra defensive(Can give Jose a run for his money) and Jota can&amp;rsquo;t even play properly as he missed a golden chance to give the ball to CR7 and took on the shot himself. I swear the game was better when Andre Silva came on. Renato Sanches as well was a star turn as they were a breath of fresh air and capitalised on a tiring Hungary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-5/</guid>
      <description>Finland v Russia Russia Domination overall. Finland did get an early chance with Pohjanpalo scoring but it was ruled out due to offside. Finally before halftime, Miranchuk scored a brilliant goal past Hradecky to get the winner. After that, a brilliant performance from Hradecky kept the score at 1-0.
Turkey v Wales Turkey were incredibly wasteful. Ramsey put Wales in front before half time. Turkey had a few good chances but the best one was put over by Yilmaz when he was right before the goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 13:32:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-3/</guid>
      <description>Netherlands v Ukraine What a thriller for the Dutch on their return to a major tounrament. First Half was all square. The second half saw a few openings and Wijnaldum scored first capitalising on the rebound from the initial save. Then, Weghorst scored although may be a foul but it was given anyway. Then the comeback happened first via a SCREAMER from Yarmolenko in the top bin and then with a header from a set piece(Maybe could be the Dutch&amp;rsquo;s undoing in this tourney).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 13:32:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-2/</guid>
      <description>Belgium v Russia This was another easy match I feel. Belgium did amazing. Lukaku strong contender for the Golden Boot. First goal was unlucky since the defender&amp;rsquo;s touch nullified the offside against Lukaku. Second one was a rebound and a good goal from Meunier. The last goal was a mere formality from Lukaku. Belgium Looking Strong.
England v Croatia An utter BOREFEST. I get that you need to defend the lead but COME ON.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 13:32:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-1/</guid>
      <description>Italy v Turkey This was inevitable. Italy just dominated. Unfortunate that the first goal was an own goal(2018 vibes anyone?). Italy could&amp;rsquo;ve had around 4 or maybe 5. The remaining 2 were easy. Immobile scoring in the rebound and Insigne curling an absolute beauty.
Wales v Switzerland Pretty good watch actually. The Welsh striker was alone mostly since Switzerland were dominating in attack. The first goal was deserved but they could&amp;rsquo;ve perhaps scored a few other chances.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>