<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Euros 2020 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Euros 2020 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 13:32:54 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 13:32:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-1/</guid>
      <description>Italy v Turkey This was inevitable. Italy just dominated. Unfortunate that the first goal was an own goal(2018 vibes anyone?). Italy could&amp;rsquo;ve had around 4 or maybe 5. The remaining 2 were easy. Immobile scoring in the rebound and Insigne curling an absolute beauty.
Wales v Switzerland Pretty good watch actually. The Welsh striker was alone mostly since Switzerland were dominating in attack. The first goal was deserved but they could&amp;rsquo;ve perhaps scored a few other chances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 13:32:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-2/</guid>
      <description>Belgium v Russia This was another easy match I feel. Belgium did amazing. Lukaku strong contender for the Golden Boot. First goal was unlucky since the defender&amp;rsquo;s touch nullified the offside against Lukaku. Second one was a rebound and a good goal from Meunier. The last goal was a mere formality from Lukaku. Belgium Looking Strong.
England v Croatia An utter BOREFEST. I get that you need to defend the lead but COME ON.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 13:32:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-3/</guid>
      <description>Netherlands v Ukraine What a thriller for the Dutch on their return to a major tounrament. First Half was all square. The second half saw a few openings and Wijnaldum scored first capitalising on the rebound from the initial save. Then, Weghorst scored although may be a foul but it was given anyway. Then the comeback happened first via a SCREAMER from Yarmolenko in the top bin and then with a header from a set piece(Maybe could be the Dutch&amp;rsquo;s undoing in this tourney).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>